class QuizQuestionUnit3 {
  int id;
  String question;
  List options;
  int correctAns;

  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      {required this.id,
      required this.question,
      required this.options,
      required this.correctAns});
}

List questionListUnit3 = [
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 1,
      question: "Polycarbonates are….",
      options: ["Polyamides", "Polyether", "Polyenes", "Polyester"],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 2,
      question: "BIOPOL is common name of ",
      options: ["PPF", "PHBV", "PPV", "Both of a & c"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 3,
      question: "Lexan is nothing but….",
      options: ["PPV", "Polyisoprene", "Kevlar", "Polycarbonat"],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 4,
      question: "Graphene is ----- conductor of electricity",
      options: ["Good", "Bad", "Semi", "None of"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 5,
      question: "Nanoplates are ---nanomaterials",
      options: ["0D", "1D", "2D", "3D"],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 6,
      question: "Nanowires are--dimensional nanomaterials",
      options: ["0D", "1D", "2D", "3D"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 7,
      question: "Nanomaterials have particle size",
      options: ["1nm-100nm", "1cm-100cm", "1mm-100mm", "1m-100m"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 8,
      question: "Polyacetylene in undoped state acts as",
      options: [
        "good conducting polymer",
        "insulator",
        "semiconductor",
        "none of these"
      ],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 9,
      question: "Smaller quantum dots emit shorter wavelength with colors",
      options: [
        "Blue and green",
        "orange and red ",
        "Blue and red",
        "green and red"
      ],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 10,
      question: "Gold nanoparticles shows which magnetic properties-",
      options: [
        "Diamagnetic",
        "ferromagnetic",
        "non magnetic",
        "none of these"
      ],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 11,
      question: "Gold nanoparticles shows which magnetic properties-",
      options: ["Diamagnetic", "ferromagnetic", "non-magnetic", "None"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 12,
      question:
          "In power plant emissions which nanomaterials used as air pollution filter? 	",
      options: ["CNT ", "Graphene", "fullerene", " Quantum Dots"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 13,
      question:
          " In propagation step the reaction intermediate of radical polymerization is ",
      options: ["Carbanion", "Carbocation ", " Carbene ", "free radical"],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 14,
      question: "Which of the following polymers are condensation polymers? ",
      options: ["Bakelite ", "Teflon", "ABS", "PS "],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 15,
      question:
          "The gold based CNT nanowires are selective and sensitive to detection of_____",
      options: ["ZnO ", "CO", "H2S", "NH3 "],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 16,
      question: "Which nanomaterials are used for Filtration?",
      options: ["CNT", "graphene", "fullerene ", "Quantum dots"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 17,
      question: "Which nanomaterial is used in QLED displays?",
      options: ["CNT", "graphene", "fullerene ", "Quantum dots"],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 18,
      question: "What is hybridization of C-atom in graphene?",
      options: ["sp", "sp2", "sp3", "sp3d2"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 19,
      question: "Glass reinforced plastic are most commonly known as _____",
      options: ["Phosphate Glass", "Glasswool", "Fibreglass", "None"],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 20,
      question: "Solution of pure buckminsterfullerene has a colour of ",
      options: ["Green", "Purple", "Pink", "Yellow"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 21,
      question: "Zero dimensional nanomaterials are--",
      options: ["CNT", "Quantum dots", "C60", "all of these"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 22,
      question:
          "A single layer of carbon atoms organized in a hexagonal lattice is called ",
      options: ["Graphite", "CNT", "Fullerene ", "Graphene "],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 23,
      question: "The colour of the nano gold particles is",
      options: ["Yellow", "Orange", "Red", "Variable"],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 24,
      question: "Quantum dots can be used in ________",
      options: [
        "Crystallography",
        "Optoelectronics",
        "Mechanics",
        "Quantum physics"
      ],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit3(
      id: 25,
      question: "How many C=C are present in polyacetylene?",
      options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      correctAns: 3),
];
